{
   "name":"quiz4",
   "que0":[
      {
         "question":"Where do you find the templates we have given you?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Inside the \"Flipping Sites\" channel.",
            "b":"Inside the \"Millionaire Access Checklist channel.",
            "c":"WE ARE NOT GIVING YOU TEMPLATES."
         },
         "answer":"c"
      },
      {
         "question":"Which mindset must you adopt?",
         "options":{
            "a":"The greedy mindset",
            "b":"The abundance mindset",
            "c":"The scared mindset",
            "d":"The hardworker mindset"
         },
         "answer":"b"
      },
      {
         "question":"If you want NEW content submit it where?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Inside of the Feedback button",
            "b":"Inside of the Ask the Professor button",
            "c":"Inside of General chat"
         },
         "answer":"a"
      },
      {
         "question":"Are you ready to proceed to the DMing Mastery section?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Of course",
            "b":"Not yet"
         },
         "answer":"a"
      }
   ],
   "que1":[
      {
         "question":"How many Effective Outreach Strategy examples did we provide you with?",
         "options":{
            "a":"7",
            "b":"5",
            "c":"6",
            "d":"4"
         },
         "answer":"a"
      },
      {
         "question":"What are Highly Needed?",
         "options":{
            "a":"High Follower Count",
            "b":"Neon Pfp and a good bio",
            "c":"Testimonials and Rapport"
         },
         "answer":"c"
      },
      {
         "question":"Do we recommend you follow up?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Of course",
            "b":"Fuck no"
         },
         "answer":"a"
      },
      {
         "question":"When are people likely to reply to you?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Having a bad profile",
            "b":"After you send them a long DM",
            "c":"Having multiple posts",
            "d": "After you send them a DM about yourself"
         },
         "answer":"c"
      },
      {
         "question":"What to do if you feel lost?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Get back to it and proceed with the simple steps",
            "b":"Take a break",
            "c":"Spam general chat"
         },
         "answer":"a"
      },
      {
         "question":"Are you ready to start DMing prospects?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Of course"
         },
         "answer":"a"
      }
   ]
}